<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on TAI SOC Blog</title>
    <link>https://tai-soc.co.ke/blog/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on TAI SOC Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2021, TAI SOC Security Analysts; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tai-soc.co.ke/blog/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TAI SOC Information Sharing and Benchmarking Program</title>
      <link>https://tai-soc.co.ke/blog/post/benchmarking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tai-soc.co.ke/blog/post/benchmarking/</guid>
      <description>The TAI SOC Information Sharing and Benchmarking Program According to Business Daily, cyberattacks on Kenyan organizations increased by roughly 50% in the months leading to 2021 compared to the previous year. According to data from the Communications Authority of Kenya, the highlighted increase was 56 million cyber threats, up from 37.1 million in 2019.
The rise can be attributed to a number of factors, including the significant shift to online operations and the current economic climate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malware Analysis</title>
      <link>https://tai-soc.co.ke/blog/post/malware-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tai-soc.co.ke/blog/post/malware-analysis/</guid>
      <description>Tai SoC Cybersecurity Spotlight: Malware Analysis It has been reported that actors working for the Russian government compromised the software supply chain of Solarwinds, an IT enterprise management company. Their goal was to distribute malicious code that would give the actors access to government and corporate networks to steal information.
Malware is at the root of many security breaches. Malware analysis is imperative to help organizations understand the extent of a malware-based attack, as seen in the FireEye example in the preceding paragraph.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
